<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Skyports Systems</title>
    <link>http://skyportsystems.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Skyports Systems</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://skyportsystems.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Sutter Hills Ventures</title>
      <link>http://skyportsystems.com/investor/sutter_hills_ventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skyportsystems.com/investor/sutter_hills_ventures/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;sutter-hills:78eb021c7004e632e22208291c61ccf6&#34;&gt;Sutter Hills&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Team</title>
      <link>http://skyportsystems.com/team/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skyportsystems.com/team/team/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our team is made up of thinkers, doers, and builders. We have some of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading experts in virtualization, cryptography, systems engineering, and networking, and we routinely uncover entirely new technological territory as we advance our solutions. We intend to stay on the leading edge, write great code, build amazing engineered systems, delight customers, and enjoy the journey as much as the destination.  We hire great people based on expertise, skill, passion and cultural fit - if this is also appealing to you, we&amp;rsquo;d love to meet you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us</title>
      <link>http://skyportsystems.com/careers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skyportsystems.com/careers/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;link rel=&#39;stylesheet&#39; href=&#39;/styles/joinus.css&#39;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;looking-for-something-new:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Looking for something new?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are an experienced, high-performance team passionate about building next-generation technology that makes a big industry impact.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#39;http://www.jobscore.com/jobs/skyportsystems&#39; class=&#39;pure-button&#39;&gt;Join Us&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stefan Dyckerhoff</title>
      <link>http://skyportsystems.com/team/stefan-dyckerhoff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skyportsystems.com/team/stefan-dyckerhoff/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Stefan was GM of routing and switching at Juniper Networks, which he originally joined as employee #33 working in chip design. He worked with Michael, Rob, and Will closely at both Juniper Networks and Cisco Systems (where he ran Enterprise routing), and brought them into Sutter Hill Ventures as Entrepreneurs-in-residence where Skyport Systems got started. Stefan holds an BS EE &amp;amp; CS from Duke University and a MS EE from Stanford University.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://skyportsystems.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skyportsystems.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#39;inner-contact&#39;&gt;
    &lt;iframe width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;450&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;border:0&#34; src=&#34;https://www.google.com/maps/embed/v1/place?q=Skyport%20Systems%2C%20Hope%20Street%2C%20Mountain%20View%2C%20CA%2C%20United%20States&amp;key=AIzaSyA4zXhojEZH8iD0rQjDTV-zceLL8JsE6Vg&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

    SKYPORT SYSTEMS
    &lt;br&gt;
    280 Hope St, Mountain View, CA 94041
    &lt;br&gt;

    &lt;a class=&#34;mail-wrapper&#34;&gt;
        &lt;i class=&#34;icon icon-mail&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
        &lt;span&gt;Drop us a note and we&#39;ll get right back to you.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;noscript&gt;Sorry, you need Javascript on to email me.&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Beesley</title>
      <link>http://skyportsystems.com/team/michaeljbeesley/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skyportsystems.com/team/michaeljbeesley/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Michael has led several routing and switching product lines at both Juniper Networks and Cisco Systems which grew to become billion-dollar annual revenue products. Michael joined Cisco Systems through their acquisition of BCN Networks, where he was the Founder and CEO, and he then joined Juniper Networks where he most recently was the CTO of the Infrastructure Products Group with Stefan. Michael holds degrees in both Mathematics and Computer Engineering from Trinity College in Dublin.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will Eatherton</title>
      <link>http://skyportsystems.com/team/will/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skyportsystems.com/team/will/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Will was VP of Engineering at Juniper Networks, where he oversaw high end routing.  Before Juniper he was 10 years at Cisco Systems as a Distinguished Engineer resulting in 24 patents.  He then led delivery of IOS-XE Operating System with a team of over 600 engineers, as well as development of a new routing system with Stefan, Michael and Rob.  He joined Cisco through their acquisition of Growth Networks, where he was a member of the founding engineering team.  He holds an EE degree from the University of Missouri-Rolla, and an MSEE from Washington University in St. Louis.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Douglas Gourlay</title>
      <link>http://skyportsystems.com/team/doug/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skyportsystems.com/team/doug/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Douglas Gourlay is responsible for all customer facing business functions at Skyport. Gourlay is an industry veteran with a track-record of success spanning twelve years at Cisco Systems as the Vice President of Product Management and Marketing for the Data Center and over five years at Arista Networks leading multiple business functions including sales, marketing, and systems engineering. Gourlay holds over forty patents on networking and systems technologies and served as a US Army Infantry Officer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rob Rodgers</title>
      <link>http://skyportsystems.com/team/rob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://skyportsystems.com/team/rob/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Rob has worked at both Cisco Systems and Juniper Networks for a cumulative 12 years and is a former principal engineer at Cisco and a former distinguished engineer at Juniper Networks. He worked closely with Michael on BCN Networks, which Cisco acquired, where he was a member of the founding engineering team. Rob holds a computer science degree from the University of Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>